Julio César Pineda Mora

Web developer

- Cali, Valle del Cauca, Colombia
 Colombian
- Website: julio.com in Julio César Pineda Mora





PROFILE

I've accumulated practical experience, emphasizing a thorough different approaches. My strong commitment to continuous learning enables me to easily adapt to new technologies and stay updated on current trends in frontend development when faced with challenges.

SKILLS

Effective communication • Cooperative mindset • Problem-solving

Resourceful approach

EDUCATION

Bogotá, Colombia SENA

08/2013 – 08/2019 Bachelor's degree in Modern Languages

Popayán, Colombia University of Cauca

♠ LANGUAGES

English (iTep C1), Spanish (Native)

COURSES

04/2023	Prompt Engineering for ChatGPT $\ \ \square$
Online	PLATZI (Online Education Platform)

07/2022 Basic Javascript ☑

Online PLATZI (Online Education Platform)

03/2022 Practical Frontend Developer ☑
Online PLATZI (Online Education Platform)

02/2022 Frontend Developer ☑

Online PLATZI (Online Education Platform)



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

02/2023 - 08/2023

Technologist in Analysis and Development of Information Systems

Popayán, Cauca,

Federación Nacional de Cafeteros de Colombia 🗷

Colombia

A dynamic Inventory Management System, developed for IT asset control within a systems office. This system encompasses a suite of modules designed for utmost efficiency, including user management with equipment transaction capabilities and many more functionalities.

Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySQL

10/2021 - 02/2023

Bilingual agent

Popayán, Cauca,

i3Net - Gobernación del Cauca 🛮

Colombia

A bilingual agent used to document and draft the academic section of beneficiary schools, while coordinating and facilitating relationships among project beneficiaries, promoting successful collaboration.

01/2019 - 12/2022

Teacher

Popayán, Cauca,

Liceo Bello Horizonte

Colombia

English teacher in charge of the high school level, responsible for the academic council of Liceo Bello Horizonte school. Additionally, a faculty member responsible for delivering lessons in ethics and

personal guidance.